(Sheldon:)Leonard, check it out.
I bought an N gage locomotive.
HaIf the size of HO.
(Sheldon:)Look, it fits in my mouth.
(Leonard:)Sounds like you had a great night.
(Howard:)I did.
(Sheldon:)- How was yours?
- Not bad.
(Leonard:)I had a lot more fun with Amy
than I thought I would.
- What do you mean by that?
- It turns out she really knows...
(Leonard:)...how to help a guy loosen up
and have a good time.
AIthough, truth be told,
my groin's a little worse for wear.
(Leonard:)Ow!
- Why'd you do that?
- To send a message.
(Sheldon:)She is not for you.
- What?
- Not for you.
(Bernadette:)Good morning, handsome.
(Howard:)Morning, Mom.
(Bernadette:)It's me.
(Howard:)Yes, it is.
And you're so pretty in the morning.
(Bernadette:)Your mom and I made you breakfast.
Oh, wow, heh,
so you guys are getting along?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, I guess.
(Bernadette:)We're very different people, Howard,
so communication's a little tricky.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Does he like the pancakes?
(Bernadette(in a similar voice):)He didn't try them yet!
- ls there any butter? Heh.
- It's butter-flavored syrup.
So? what's the word?
(Bernadette:)He wants butter!
It's butter-flavored syrup!
(Bernadette:)I just told him that!
(Howard:)I don't need any butter.
(Bernadette:)If you want butter, I'll get you butter.
Well, I guess I'll cut these by myseIf.